tdpri.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy

Because protecting your privacy is very important to GearTalk Network we have established this Privacy Policy which explains what information we collect from our visitors, how we use that information, and how you can view or contro thel use of the information you submit. Please note that this policy may be revised from time to time without notice, so please check it frequently.

## Personal Information

GearTalk Network asks for personal information only when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). For example, GearTalk Network asks for your name, email address, and location when you register, and collects additional information for surveys or other promotions sponsored by GearTalk Network and/or its promotional partners. We use your Personal Information to operate GearTalk Network's services, and to help identify you and gather broad demographic information. 

## Cookies

GearTalk Network or its advertisers may place a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. Cookies are small pieces of information or files that are stored on a user's computer by the Web server through a user's browser for record keeping purposes. The information can be retrieved to personalize, monitor, or regulate use of the site. Cookies allow GearTalk Network to automate access and data entry functions of the site, such as login information, and tailor the site to a user's preferences or interests. In addition, cookies allow GearTalk Network to track usage of the site to determine those areas of the site that are useful or popular (and those that are not), thereby enabling GearTalk Network to improve and update its service. 

## Direct Mailings and "Opting In"

GearTalk Network may send you information about various products and services that may be of interest to you. When you register for membership on any of our WEBSITES you grant the COMPANY permission to send these communications to you. You may opt-out of some of these communications. Other communications, such as notices from Administrators or Moderators may not be unsubscribed without deactivating your account. You may deactivate your account anytime upon written request.

## Public Forums

GearTalk Network offers User provided content. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose Personal Information to other users or third parties on the GearTalk Network WEBSITES, or through email, or outside of the GearTalk Network system, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other members or parties. While GearTalk Network strives to protect your Personal Information, GearTalk Network cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to GearTalk Network and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. Please be aware that member's email addresses are displayed by default on our WEBSITES. However, members may, at their option, take steps to restrict the display of their email addresses to everyone except Administrators and Moderators through various settings in the Profile on our WEBSITES. 

## Links to Other Websites

GearTalk Network may provide links to its partners and other non-affiliated Internet websites. These sites have separate data and privacy practices independent of GearTalk Network and GearTalk Network disclaims any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. 

## Correcting and Updating Your Information

You can view and make changes to the information you have previously provided to GearTalk Network by visiting your online Profile (UserCP) on each of our WEBSITES. 

## Security

To protect the security of your Personal Information, GearTalk Network limits access to user data to authorized GearTalk Network personnel. GearTalk Network will NOT disclose any Personal Information except as described above or in its Terms & Conditions. GearTalk Network may disclose user information, including demographic data, in an aggregated form that does not identify individual users in order to describe its services to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties and for other lawful purposes. GearTalk Network may disclose information about you if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of GearTalk Network or others. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you believe GearTalk Network has not adhered to these principles, please contact us at: [webmaster@geartalknet.com](mailto:webmaster@geartalknet.com)
